

Senior Line Incharge specializing for manage cycletime. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic projects. Wellversed in numerous program including 5S, 7QC tool, TPM activity, manpower handling. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

TUSHAR RAMANUJ

Phone:

+91 9638526367, 9773202281

E-Mail:

mr.ramanuj0408@gmail.com

DOB: 24/01/1995

Address:

<u>T</u>o: Dolatpura Ta: Viramagam Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India 382150

Skill Highlights

- Positive attitude
- Ready to learn new things
- Target achievement
- Kaizen implementation
- Shift control
- Line balancing
- Team management

Experience

04/08/2020 TO CONTINUE

JUNIER ENGINNER - P C Patel Mahalaxmi Infra LLP

03/2018 to 10/2019

LINE INCHARGE - SHEKHANI PVT. LTD., SANNAD

 Shekhani Pvt. Ltd. in a production is sanitary napkin for product name is wonder wings.

02/2017 to 03/2018

JUNIOR ENGINEER - SONO COYO STEERING SYSTEM LIMITED, SANNAD

- ISO/TS certified Company is a deeming awarded company & having technical and financial collaboration with JETET (koyo Seiko) japan.
- specializing for manage cycle time. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic projects. Wellversed in numerous program including 5S, 7QC tool, TPM activity, manpower handling. Strong background in project management and customer relations.
- Sono koyo Steering system is being engaged in manufacturing & supplying steering and transmission to MUL, TKML, GMI, HML, USA & Lotus UK.
- The annual turnover of the company is approx. Rs.3500cr.

09/2013 to 02/2017

TEAM LEADER - UTKRASH MANUFACTURING CO., AHMEDABAD

 Company for job shop in CNC, VMC Machinery. Work to be line control.

Education

2011-2013

Diploma in Mechanical: K.P. Thakkar institute of engineering Sokli, Viramgam, Ahmedabad. (GTU)

Diploma pass in 2013 with 6.35 CGPA.

Certifications

Cre-o 2.0, pro-e, AutoCAD, MS office